Straight up, I just use block as an
emergency tool now. Like, okay, here's
the way I see guest, all right? The way
I see guest is just pure knockback set
mode. Make as much use of elevation as
you can. You got charge, you got punch.
And that's pretty much that.
The block is just like
damage negation if you can. If you
really can react parry, then
I mean, if you can react block, then
sure, you can do that. I'm not really
built for that though. I haven't got
that good reaction time. Maybe against
John Doe I can, but the thing is,
against John Doe, you can't even parry
John Doe because he has unstoppable. If
he save your punch,
all it's going to do is reset your punch
cool down. You shouldn't parry because
he could just unstoppable and it's like
yeah.
And you can't save your punch,
the stun at least, for
later anymore. So,
Oh.
All right, bro.
All right, if I can try to get a punch,
that'd be really nice.
Where did he
Hello?
That actually worked.
Oh, I was about to do that, man. Shoot.
Poor coordination, that sucks. Oh, and
I'm not there to punch.
Oh, you are screwed.
Where's the John Doe?
Where did he Oh, what?
I don't even know what just happened.
What is happening now?
I don't know what hit me.
It is honestly like a nice place to
start a chase against the John Doe
specifically.
Just cuz of like the other areas are
kind of traps.
Uh, I kind of want to help that guest
out.
Where'd
Dude, I can't predict their movement.
They just keep making 180s.
There we go. Little charge.
Yikes.
Okay.
Not looking good.
I'll be able to go for like punch here.
Oh, he put a footprint up there again.
That sucks.
Uh
Yeah, I knew he was about to do some
crap like that.
He doesn't have a foot- Oh, he does have
a footprint there.
He placed it like wrong though. He
should have put it like here so it also
blocks this.
Oh, that would be hilarious if I get
trapped in there.
I might have to help them out.
Oh, yikes.
Hold on, let me try to get around.
Please don't stay in there. Please don't
Did they jump over or something? Where's
the V?
Dude, I'm actually clueless. What is
happening right now?
Oh, the V disconnected.
Okay.
Uh I'm not going to stay up there.
That's a death trap.
I might try to help them though.
Oh wait, they could just jump over.
Okay, that's nice.
Little charge.
Help them out.
Got to make a good angle here.
Can try to trap the chance in there.
Probably.
Is he going for the
He's killing the Jane.
You want to save the Jane for LMS.
Did you do unstoppable that? He did not.
Hold on, that's kind of susy.
But the chance is there too.
I just didn't actually clueless this
entire game.
Wait, please.
No, I got to get in there. No.
My fault, bro. We got separated. He's
probably leaving the Jane like low
though, and then he's going to go after
me.
Right?
What? Okay.
I could have been there. Wait till he
has one there,
one there, and I believe one there.
Okay, so this entire part of the map is
free.
There we go. A little bit of knockback.
I try to flick it. Okay, no.
I could try to punch.
All right.
I'm trying to play really safe.
Okay.
Here is like relatively free cuz he
doesn't have any footprints.
And then so far we could just like loop
this. He'll probably cut it off at some
point though.
Right now.
Block that for the resistance.
We could loop this right now since he
doesn't have spikes.
But being here in general Oh, I clipped
myself on that. It got me damage, bro.
Okay, right now.
Oh, it's kind of awkward. He could trap
me up there.
I don't have block back. Okay, we're
good.
Uh
Going in here is really weird.
Oh, he doesn't see me.
Okay, what I can do,
go here.
Oh, he's about to like drop on me
actually.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm not going to go for anything risky.
I got to block this
for the resistance.
There we go.
First game. Guess 666 is kind of
tough now as guest because now that I've
in my opinion, now that you feel more
knockback focused
it's like guess 666 takes a lot less
knockback.
So it's kind of like what the hell.
And you can't really block Demonic
Pursuit either so if they like jump over
the obstacle you're looping and then
like yeah, that that doesn't sound fun.
Hold on.
Oh, well.
Does he live? He does not live.
Oh, he's going after me.
This is not good.
He can jump over this loop but it's like
the best we have on this map.
Okay.
weird
Okay, the thing is still I'm holding on.
We got a little punch.
I was going to just go after me with
that.
You could have got me there.
That'd be really bad.
Okay, we got to help him out.
Oh, I knocked him into him, bro.
Not my fault he did like completely
random direction.
Hold on. There's still a chance I could
block.
Honestly right now that guy's in an
emergency.
All right.
Where's he going?
Oh,
Okay, this should be a pretty nice loop
over here actually now that I look at
it.
This one looks kind of nice. I think he
might clip onto this.
Oh, that is not good.
Hold on.
Yikes.
Can't even get there inside, man.
Might demonic pursuit.
I pressed block. What?
I literally pressed block, dude.
I should have reduced the damage.
Okay.
I'll only use the charge if like he's
literally right on top of me because
if I do it just like to do the
knockback, then
you know, I kind of like charge towards
him to do that, so
That's really bad. That's really
No. No.
You lost that back?
Okay, I could have done the wall. That's
W.
Oh, yikes.
Okay, nice.
Yeah, this is like the best loop we have
on this map.
There's not much we can Nobody's
helping, dude. There's no taunt throwing
traps in here. There's no guest.
I'm not going to block
unless it's like
I don't even know.
Okay, is he going to just get blood hunt
and then go for me?
Yikes, dude.
What's he doing like the blood rush
thing where you do it farther away so it
last longer?
Yeah, that's what he's doing.
Might infernal cry is here.
Okay.
He didn't hit his cry, so that's good,
but
Oh, I'm Oh, is he Did he farm blood that
way?
Oh, is that a method? I don't know the
sixer method like that. Do you like farm
blood by going away and then I bleed out
more.
Like more of those blood orbs. I think
that's what he did.
Also, that was a really lucky block
earlier.
Okay, well, there's at least a trap
there.
Trap there.
I like keep note of that.
Oh, the top is dying. Should try to help
them
a little bit. Still the timer out.
You got to be careful though cuz
if I'm near the sixer when I'm not at
that god loop, dude,
it's kind of scary.
Did it even knock him back?
I have to like punch this dude to affect
him. Oh.
Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
Let's give him demonic pursuit.
Oh, no.
He's going to infernal cry probably when
I'm lower stamina.
Oh, no. Not even.
Okay, he's on cool down. Do that.
Okay.
Uh.
Nice. Little bit of a stun. Barely
anything.
Okay, he didn't hit that.
Come on.
Uh, come on.
It's Oh, I thought he was going to get
on top of it. That would be so much
worse.
Okay.
Uh.
So rough.
Yikes.
So scary, dude.
Uh, get away from me.
React. No. No. I wasn't shift locked. I
wasn't shift locked. I was aiming at
him, but I wasn't shift locked. Okay,
we're going to go to this other god
loop.
Oh.
Okay, this one isn't as good, honestly.
I'm trying to get to the other one.
Oh, please.
Other guest, please. Okay, it's really
low. I could block.
Come on.
Let's go.
Bro, that was so crazy, dude. Holy crap.
All right, no sweat to you.
It's an interesting match up. We got
this map, so
we got some elevation there and some
elevation there, and that should be
pretty useful. What is he doing?
Kind of got to be careful of like a
straight blood hook.
I'm ass.
All right, hold on.
Going to help out with the punch.
Okay.
Dude, where are we going?
Better stay clear of that.
Cataclysm of doom.
I wasn't there in time to block him.
Ah, wrong animation.
That was the hunter's feast animation. I
reacted wrong thing.
All right, dude.
I'm screwed.
Um
Wait, did he Oh, yeah, he's flying.
Hold up.
He hit someone.
I don't know what's happening right now,
man.
He's there now.
All right, that guy is dead.
Like I don't know where people are going
to pass, man. I don't know how to like
get ahead.
Uh
What is happening?
Oh my goodness, I'm ass.
Please say this isn't blocked. Okay,
it's not.
Someone say block, like block? Oh, and
that guy is not dead, actually.
You know what? Maybe he is dead.
Uh
I really want to help you, man.
Against Nosferatu, like you can barely
even react block cuz he has a billion
just animations.
WHAT ARE we passing? The
Everything I'm Okay.
Different man, I'm sick of I misclicked.
Different man, I'm sick of people taking
these random 180s when I'm trying to
help.
Like shoot, and that hits me cuz of
course it does.
Dude,
I am so sick of this.
I just want to play Veronica again, man.
Bump is like
all the help I need.
All the helping tool I need.
Okay, nice. I got to hit a parry.
Uh
Where's the killer?
No charge.
Is it Billy and then Oh, I'm not going
to be able to see that. I am sorry.
Um
Okay.
After trying to get up there, oh
you're screwed. You're
You're just screwed.
No other way to put it.
Where is Jane?
Is Jane good?
Oh, hell no. He's up there.
Yeah, we're going to try to help Jane
out, okay?
Oh, you are just kind of screwed, mate.
Wait, are you?
Come on, just come out here. Please.
No.
No. Don't do it. Don't do it.
I'm sorry, Jane. That that that had to
have been like the worst
milestone for for what, man?
Milestone for
for absolutely what?
Okay, we got out of there.
My blood hook. Not blood hooking yet.
Little mind game. Kind of scary.
We're not looping very tight. Not tight
enough, bro. Here's a Billy animation,
so I'm not going to go for like some
Okay.
I'll be able to charge him up here.
There we go.
Oh, I should have waited for that one.
Okay. So, we cut off the loop, but we
can just go over here. Might be flying.
Yeah, he is.
Oh, okay.
Oh, shoot. I should have just kept going
up.
I cannot see
him.
He needs to react.
Oh, watch this. Watch this. Watch this.
Okay.
Around the corner. Why are you using
that right now?
Oh, jeez.
Where's the game ever? Of course it's
gold kid.
All right, so
we're charging minions.
And that's all I'm freaking doing for
this team, bro. I swear at this point.
Come on, give me those minions. Get over
here.
And that's all the freaking utility we
have.
I guess I could punch, bro. Wait.
Please.
Uh
Okay, he switched off pretty quick.
Oh, and if I can go over here, please.
Just pass here.
Please don't use bubble Okay,
there we go.
Okay, we started with full stamina, so
my walk speed
Bro.
Come on now, please.
These minions.
Just going to go up here. Our charge
gets value here.
Oh, you can switch targets.
Yo.
Oh my gosh. That was
That goes in an edit, bro. That That's
going in an edit, okay?
Someone make an edit of that.
Nobody's making an edit of that.
Wait.
Oh, they know the W spot. I like this
guy.
Let's just screw that.
Yo.
Okay.
Kind of useless-ish.
Surprise.
OH.
IT WORKED.
IT WORKED. OH MY GOSH. BRO, I freaking
so much I think normally finally I could
do something that works.
Okay. Okay, go up here. Go up here. Oh,
you're dead. You're just dead.
I'm sorry, folk. You're dead.
Just distract Oh.
Okay, you know I could just charge you,
sir. Oh, shoot. Oh, shoot. He waited. He
waited, BRO. WAIT.
I'M COOKED. I'M COOKED. I'M COOKED. I'M
COOKED. I'M COOKED. I need help. I need
help. I need help. I need help, please.
I need help.
Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
We're going to be okay. We're going to
be okay. We're going to be okay. We're
going to be okay. Just Just get my
stamina back.
Stop being stupid.
Okay. We go over there.
Careful of the walk speed and the
corrupt and the everything.
Okay.
Okay, 19 minutes, bro. We can live that.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Where are they?
Where are they? Where are they?
This is scary. This is sketchy. I'm
going to go to this back door. They're
not going to notice me, bro.
All skill. But anyway,
that's my stuff for you guys. Gameplay
by Matty Slays.
Yep.